Big Dreamers Dream Big
Elliot: The Littlest Reindeer is a animation, family,
adventure film directed by Jennifer Westcott.
When Blitzen announces his retirement on December 21st, a miniature horse has 3 days to fulfill
his lifelong dream of earning a spot on Santa's team at the North Pole try-outs.
Elliot (voice), played by Josh Hutcherson.
Hazel (voice), played by Samantha Bee.
Corkie (voice), played by Morena Baccarin.
Donner (voice), played by John Cleese.
Lemondrop / Ludzinka / Blitzen (voice), played by Martin Short.
Santa (voice), played by George Buza.
Elliot the Littlest Reindeer is a 2018 Canadian animated Christmas film written and directed by Jennifer Wescott and
featuring the voices of Josh Hutcherson, Samantha Bee, Martin Short, Morena Baccarin, Jeff Dunham and John Cleese.
When Blitzen retires from Santa's reindeer team, Elliot and
his friend Hazel travel to the North Pole.
As Elliot  takes on the North Pole tryouts, Hazel learns
that Christmas may be headed for disaster.
Meanwhile, back at their farm, a sinister lady threatens the lives of their
friends, and Elliot is faced with the biggest decision of his life.
The film explores themes of holiday, santa claus, horse, retirement, reindeer.